Contact

831 - College Fishery Link Road, Harua, Kishoreganj -2300. +8801833108338 (Mobile) muin.bd@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/ muinchowdhury (LinkedIn) www.aureliait.com (Company)

Top Skills

Windows System Administration Windows 7 Windows 8.1

Languages

English (Professional Working)
Bangla (Native or Bilingual)

Certifications

Microsoft Certified Solutions Associate (MCSA)

Muin Chowdhury

Freelance IT Pro, Front-End Web Developer & Web Researcher Kishoreganj District

Summary

I'm a certified IT Professional with 7 years of professional experience. My expertise covers Networking Technologies and System Administration in Windows Client OS and Servers & Linux Distro and Servers.

I do Web Researching jobs professionally as well for a very long time. I like to do this type of job as it requires various methods and investigations to find the correct contacts and information from WWW proactively.

I also like to code front-end web development with HTML5, CSS3, Bootstrap, basic JavaScript, and WordPress customization with SEO and responsive mobile-first web development.

I always try to work dedicatedly and deliver my best quality to maintain a high standard.

Experience

Aurelia IT
Founder
October 2018 - Present (3 years 5 months)
Kishoreganj Sadar, Dhaka, Bangladesh

Training & Outsourcing Agency

Upwork 7 years 9 months

Technical Support Agent for App at OMS April 2018 - Present (3 years 11 months)

Web Researcher at WWC
June 2014 - Present (7 years 9 months)

Hamid Fabrics Limited Sr. Executive, IT October 2014 - January 2015 (4 months) Narsinghdi

Full IT Support in Textile Factory Region.

Scholastica Limited
Officer- IT Support
February 2014 - March 2014 (2 months)
Dhaka

LAN Support, OS Deploy, Software Installation, End users IT Supports, CPU Components Assembling or Replacing, Network and Printer Troubleshooting, IT support over Telephone & by Remote Desktop Connections.

Education

IDB-BISEW IT Scholarship Project
Diploma of Education, System, Networking, and LAN/WAN Management/
Manager · (2012 - 2013)

Dhaka College, Dhaka Master's Degree, English (2010 - 2011)

Nasirabad College, Mymensingh Bachelor's Degree, Social Science · (2005 - 2008)

Gurudayal Govt. College, Kishoreganj HSC, Science · (2000 - 2001)

Kishoreganj Govt. Boys' High School, Kishoreganj High School, Science · (1997 - 1998)